bubbler.me 2018-12-15

# Bubbler.me - Privacy Policy

Bubbler.me operates http://bubbler.me. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

### Information Collection And Use

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name ("Personal Information").

### Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

### Information Collection And Use

Bubbler.me rents Google AdSense space on its webpages as a form of raising funds to maintain this website. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits on Bubbler.me. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to Bubbler.me users based on their visits here and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings (<http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>).

Bubbler.me throught Google AdSense may use third-party vendors and ad networks serving ads. Bubbler.me users can opt out of some third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting aboutads.info (http://www.aboutads.info/).

Bubbler.me is using Google Analytics to collect traffic data in order to better understand our users needs and improve website functionality. Google AdSense, Google Analytics and other third-party vendors use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) or other first-party identifiers, and third-party cookies (such as Google advertising cookies). Visitors can opt-out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features, including through Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means (for example, the NAI's consumer opt-out). Google Analytics currently available opt-outs for the web (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Information We Collect Automatically

We use technologies like cookies and pixel tags to provide, monitor, analyze, promote and improve the Service. For example, a cookie is used to remember your user name when you return to the Service and to improve our understanding of how you interact with the Service. You can block cookies on your web browser; however please be aware that some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

### Log Files

When you use the Service, our servers automatically record certain information in server logs. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, mobile carrier, and other such information. Log files help us to monitor, analyze, improve and maintain the Service and to diagnose and fix any Service-related issues.

### Device Identifiers.

When you access the Service using a mobile device, we collect specific device information contained in your mobile device’s “device identifier.” This device identifier includes information such as the type of device you are using, its operating system, and mobile network information, which may include your mobile phone number. We may associate this device identifier with your Service account and will use data associated with your device identifier to customize our Services to your device and to analyze any device-related issues.

### Location Information

We may collect and process information about the location of the device from which you are accessing the Service. Location data may convey information about how you browse the Service and may be used in conjunction with personally identifiable information. You can disable location based services in settings associated with the Service; however please be aware that some features of the Service may not function properly if location services are turned off.

### How We Share Your Information

We may share the information we collect from you with third parties as detailed below.

As Directed By You  
We will display your Profile information on your profile page and elsewhere on the Service in accordance with the preferences you set in your account. You can review and revise your Profile information at any time.

We will display your Content within the Service as directed by you.  
If you elect to use a third party application to access the Service, then we may share or disclose your account and Profile information and your Content with that third party application as directed by you. Please remember that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties so you should make sure you trust the application and that it has a privacy policy acceptable to you.

With Trusted Service Providers and Business Partners.  
We may utilize trusted third party service providers to assist us in delivering our Service. For example, we may use third parties to help host our Service, send out email updates, or process payments. These service providers may have access to your information) for the limited purpose of providing the service we have contracted with them to provide. They are required to have a privacy policy and security standards in place that are at least as protective of your information as is this Privacy Policy. We may also store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Bubbler (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

With Law Enforcement or In Order to Protect Our Rights.  
We may disclose your information (including your personally identifiable information) if required to do so by law or subpoena and if the relevant request meets our Law Enforcement Guidelines. We may also disclose your information to our legal counsel, governmental authorities or law enforcement if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to do so in order to comply with a law or regulation; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Bubbler’s rights or property.

In an Aggregate and Non-Personally Identifiable Manner.  
We may disclose aggregate non-personally identifiable information (such as aggregate and anonymous usage data, platform types, etc.) about the overall use of our Service publicly or with interested third parties to help them understand, or to help us improve, the Service.

In Connection With a Sale or Change of Control. If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes, we may transfer your information to the new owner so that the Service can continue to operate. In such case, your information would remain subject to the promises and commitments contained in this Privacy Policy until such time as this Privacy Policy is updated or amended by the acquiring party upon notice to you.

### Links to Other Web Sites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to from within the Service, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect and your activities on that third party website is subject to such third party website’s own rules and policies.

### Do Not Track Signals

Some browsers have a “do not track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. We currently do not respond to “do not track” signals.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### Contact Us

For questions about these or any Bubbler terms or policies, email us at contact@bubbler.me.
